Guide to the Rudolf Carnap Papers, 1904-2007 ASP.1974.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Name Index, XXVII.
  - Kaplan, Abraham (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, Abraham (Box 109, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 6)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 80, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 85, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 88, Folder 41, Item 8)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 88, Folder 62, Item 2)
    (sequestered)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 88, Folder 67, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 92, Folder 22, Item 3)
  - Kaplan, David (Box 102, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - Kaplan, Iona (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, Iona (Box 102, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Kaplan, Jeremiah (Box 88, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Kaplan, Rudolf (Box 88, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Kasjer, A. (Box 102, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Kasner, Edward (Box 90, Folder 81, Item 1)
  - Kasperle (Box 102, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Kasperle (Box 102, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Katz, Aaron (Box 27, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - Kaufman, E. W. (Box 83, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Kaufmann, Agnes (Box 27, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Kaufmann, Agnes (Box 102, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Kaufmann, Agnes (Box 102, Folder 25, Item 53)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 28, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 28, Folder 20, Item 6)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 28, Folder 21, Item 25)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 28, Folder 22, Item 21)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 28, Folder 23, Item 24)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 28, Folder 24, Item 8)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 28, Folder 25, Item 15)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 28, Folder 26, Item 4)
  - Kaufmann, Felix (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Kaufmann, Reinhaed (Box 102, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Kaufmannm William (Box 27, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Kawczak, Andezej (Box 27, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Kazantzakes, Nikos (Box 90, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Kazemier, B. H. (Box 27, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Kecskemeti, Paul (Box 88, Folder 42, Item 3)
  - Kelly, Allan (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, Jenifer (Box 83, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 78, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 78, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 78, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 78, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 78, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 81, Folder 65, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 80, Folder 17, Item 5)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 82, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 82, Folder 30, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 83, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 83, Folder 15, Item 31)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 83, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 83, Folder 17, Item 22)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 82, Folder 18, Item 26)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 83, Folder 19, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 83, Folder 22, Item 8)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 83, Folder 23, Item 6)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 84, Folder 45, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 84, Folder 74, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 88, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 91, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 93, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 93, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 93, Folder 22, Item 30)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 93, Folder 19, Item 10)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 93, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 93, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 93, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 93, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 94, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 95, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 102, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 107, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 109, Folder 53, Item 1)
  - Kemeny, John G. (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 2)
  - Kemeny, Robbie and Jenny (Box 83, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Kendall, Maurice G. (Box 94, Folder 25, Item 3)
  - Kent, Francis B. (Box 102, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Kerr, Clark (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 3)
  - Kerr, Clark (Box 85, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Kerr, Clark (Box 85, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Kerr, Clark (Box 90, Folder 72, Item 1)
  - Ketonen, Oiva (Box 27, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - Kewer, L. J. (Box 27, Folder 56, Item 2)
  - Kiermaier, Rudolf (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Kindt, Werner (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - King, Guido (Box 27, Folder 59, Item 1)
  - King, Helen (Box 90, Folder 72, Item 1)
  - King, Thomas (Box 85, Folder 62, Item 1)
  - Kirk, Grayson (Box 90, Folder 72, Item 5)
  - Klatt, Fritz (Box 28, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Kleene, S. C. (Box 88, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - Kleinsmid, Shirley Von (Box 102, Folder 42, Item 2)
  - Klemke, E. D. (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 5)
  - Klibansky, Raymond (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Kline, George (Box 90, Folder 60, Item 1)
  - Kline, J. R. (Box 81, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Klopfer, Bruno (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Klopfer, Bruno and Erma (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Klopfer, Bruno and Erma (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Klopfer, Bruno and Erma (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Klopsteg, Paul E. (Box 91, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Kneale, W. (Box 27, Folder 46, Item 2)
  - Kneale, W. (Box 88, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Knighl, Helen (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Koch, Lucy (Box 85, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Kochen, Manfred (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Kockelmans, Joseph J. (Box 27, Folder 36, Item 3)
  - Konvitz, Milton R. (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Korner, S. (Box 88, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Korner, S. (Box 94, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Korth, Georg (Box 27, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Kracke, Virgina L. (Box 85, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Kraft, Victor (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 1)
  - Kraft, Victor (Box 27, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Kraft, Victor (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 3)
  - Kraft, Victor (Box 88, Folder 46, Item 4)
  - Kraft, Victor (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Kranz, Fay (Box 80, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Kranz, Fay (Box 91, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Kraus, Doris (Box 91, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Kraus, Oskar (Box 28, Folder 28, Item 4)
  - Krauss, Peter (Box 80, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Krauss, Peter (Box 82, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Krauss, Peter (Box 83, Folder 23, Item 9)
  - Krauss, Peter (Box 83, Folder 24, Item 41)
  - Krauss, Peter (Box 83, Folder 26, Item 3)
  - Krauss, Peter (Box 83, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Krauss, Peter (Box 83, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Krauss, Peter (Box 83, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Krauth, Lothar (Box 88, Folder 47, Item 5)
  - Kries-Schneeberger, J. (Box 95, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Kroiss, Gerhardt (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 7)
  - Kroy, M. (Box 102, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Kruger, Lorenz (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 5)
  - Kruth, Joseph Wood (Box 85, Folder 62, Item 1)
  - Kuhn, Thomas S. (Box 82, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Kuhn, Thomas S. (Box 88, Folder 47, Item 4)
  - Kuhn, Thomas S. (Box 88, Folder 70, Item 1)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 82, Folder 21, Item 3)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 82, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 10)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 82, Folder 24, Item 10)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 89, Folder 55, Item 1)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 92, Folder 13, Item 6)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 92, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 92, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 92, Folder 29, Item 8)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 92, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 92, Folder 36, Item 3)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 92, Folder 37, Item 1)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 93, Folder 56, Item 1)
  - Kuhns, John Lary (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Kungermacher, Aug A. (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Kursunoglu, Behram (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Kurtz, Paul (Box 27, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Kurtz, Paul (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 2)
  - Kurtz, Paul (Box 88, Folder 59, Item 1)
  - Kyburg, Henry E. (Box 84, Folder 35, Item 5)
  - Kyburg, Henry E. (Box 84, Folder 36, Item 16)
  - Kyburg, Henry E. (Box 107, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Lacha, John (Box 27, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - La Couse, Guerin (Box 27, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Lagnel, Fred (Box 95, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Laing, G. J. (Box 89, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Lakatos, Imre (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 2)
  - Lakatos, Imre (Box 27, Folder 48, Item 30)
  - Lakatos, Imre (Box 27, Folder 50, Item 1)
  - Lakatos, Imre (Box 88, Folder 49, Item 5)
  - Lakatos, Imre (Box 102, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Lakatos, Imre (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 2)
  - Lambert, Karel (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Landrock, George M. (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 5)
  - Lange, M. (Box 81, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Lange, Otto (Box 27, Folder 59, Item 52)
  - Lange, Otto (Box 85, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - Laqueur, Walter (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Lash, Joseph P. (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Laso, Jose Averez (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Laso, Jose Averez (Box 88, Folder 50, Item 7)
  - Lauer, Theodore L. (Box 90, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Lauter, Elva and Hal (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Lauter, Hal (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Lauter, Hal (Box 107, Folder 3, Item 14)
  - Lauter, Herman A. (Box 85, Folder 50, Item 5)
  - Lavely, John H. (Box 85, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Law, Yip-Wang (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Lawson, Warren (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 7)
  - Lazarsfeld, Paul (Box 90, Folder 68, Item 2)
  - Lazerwitz, Morris (Box 88, Folder 51, Item 6)
  - Leblanc, Hugues (Box 84, Folder 36, Item 33)
  - Leblanc, Hugues (Box 81, Folder 10, Item 35)
  - Leep, Hana Jurgen (Box 27, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Leeuwen, J. K. W. Van (Box 85, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Lefkowitz, Louis J. (Box 94, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Lehrer, Keith (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Lehrer, Keith (Box 84, Folder 37, Item 4)
  - Lehrer, Keith (Box 102, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Leijohnufvund, Axel (Box 88, Folder 52, Item 3)
  - Leijohnufvund, Axel (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Leinfellner, Werner (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Leinfellner, Werner (Box 88, Folder 52, Item 8)
  - Lenz, John W. (Box 27, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Lenz, John W. (Box 82, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Lenz, John W. (Box 89, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - Leonard, Henry S. (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Leonard, Henry S. (Box 110, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Le Seur, Eduard (Box 89, Folder 74, Item 5)
  - Lessing, Fredinand (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Levi, Albert (Box 27, Folder 11, Item 5)
  - Levi, Issac (Box 84, Folder 38, Item 10)
  - Levine, Philip (Box 80, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Levy, P. (Box 81, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Lewis, David (Box 80, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Lewis, David (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Lewis, David (Box 80, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Lewis, David (Box 88, Folder 53, Item 4)
  - Lhamon, Deborah (Box 82, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Lieber, Hugh G. (Box 27, Folder 11, Item 5)
  - Lieber, Hugh G. (Box 89, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Liebman, Arthur (Box 90, Folder 47, Item 1)
  - Liebman, Arthur (Box 90, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Lilly, Mary Jane (Box 90, Folder 59, Item 1)
  - Lindbekk, Torre (Box 89, Folder 45, Item 2)
  - Linsky, Leonard (Box 91, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Lipton, Nettie (Box 85, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - L'Isle, Roller De (Box 28, Folder 19, Item 2)
  - Lettauer, Sebastian B. (Box 102, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Locchiarella (Box 84, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Loehrich, Rolf (Box 27, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Loehrich, Rolf (Box 88, Folder 53, Item 1)
  - Loehrich, Rolf (Box 88, Folder 55, Item 6)
  - Lohmann (Box 81, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Lohmann (Box 81, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Long, Robert (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Lool, Ismer and Mia (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Lorenzen, Paul (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 4)
  - Lorenzen, Paul (Box 88, Folder 55, Item 10)
  - Loth, Nina (Box 81, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Low, S. M. (Box 88, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Lowanberg, Erna (Box 82, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Lowanberg, Erna (Box 102, Folder 31, Item 28)
  - Lowanberg, Erna (Box 102, Folder 33, Item 45)
  - Luhow, Neil B. (Box 80, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Lucal, John A. (Box 94, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Luckenbach, Sidney A. (Box 88, Folder 57, Item 2)
  - Lutman, Marie K. (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 6)
  - Lutterotti, M. Von (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Lynch, H. A. (Box 102, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Lynch, Lawrence E. (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - MacKay, A. B. (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Mac Lane, Saunders (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Macqueen, James B. (Box 85, Folder 57, Item 1)
  - Madden, Edward H. (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Madden, Edward H. (Box 27, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Maja (Box 21, Folder 74, Item 1)
  - Mallory, George (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Mandelbaum, Maurice (Box 85, Folder 39, Item 3)
  - Mandelbaum, Maurice (Box 90, Folder 75, Item 1)
  - Manicas, Peter T. (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 3)
  - Marble, R. C. (Box 95, Folder 21, Item 4)
  - Marcuse, Herbert (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Marcuse, Herbert (Box 88, Folder 59, Item 1)
  - Marc-Woqau, Hugo B. (Box 88, Folder 51, Item 1)
  - Margenau, Henry (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - Margolis, Joseph (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 5)
  - Markovic, Kristine (Box 88, Folder 59, Item 2)
  - Markovic, Mihailo (Box 88, Folder 59, Item 13)
  - Marschak, Jacob (Box 85, Folder 57, Item 3)
  - Marsh, H. Clifton (Box 90, Folder 74, Item 3)
  - Martin, Marianne (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Martin, Michael (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 3)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 80, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 81, Folder 12, Item 44)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 88, Folder 60, Item 24)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Martin, Richard (Box 109, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Martinet, Andre (Box 95, Folder 28, Item 2)
  - Marquis (Box 80, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Masani, P. (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Massey, Gerald J. (Box 90, Folder 40, Item 7)
  - Mates, Benson (Box 85, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Mates, Benson (Box 85, Folder 41, Item 1)
  - Mates, Benson (Box 88, Folder 15, Item 7)
  - Mates, Benson (Box 88, Folder 62, Item 1)
  - Mathers, Robert Leslie (Box 85, Folder 43, Item 1)
  - Mathers, Robert Leslie (Box 88, Folder 63, Item 10)
  - Mathers, Ruth Anna (Box 85, Folder 51, Item 5)
  - Matherson, Erika (Box 88, Folder 64, Item 1)
  - Matherson, Gordon (Box 88, Folder 64, Item 15)
  - Mathias, James F. (Box 83, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Mathias, James F. (Box 88, Folder 60, Item 1)
  - Mathias, James F. (Box 88, Folder 61, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 81, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 82, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 82, Folder 22, Item 4)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 4)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 84, Folder 59, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 88, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 92, Folder 19, Item 6)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 92, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 92, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 92, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 92, Folder 26, Item 4)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 92, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 93, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 93, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 93, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 93, Folder 36, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 93, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 93, Folder 41, Item 8)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 94, Folder 40, Item 2)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 95, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Matthews, Gordon (Box 109, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Matthews, L. J. (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 4)
  - Matthews, Mrs. L. J. (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 3)
  - Mauchlan, Errol W. (Box 90, Folder 70, Item 3)
  - Maxwell, Grover (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 5)
  - Maxwell, Grover (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Maxwell, Grover (Box 89, Folder 25, Item 3)
  - Maxwell, Grover (Box 90, Folder 63, Item 1)
  - Maxwell, Grover (Box 102, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Maxwell, Grover (Box 102, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - May, Sybil H. (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - McCartney, Mary Ellen (Box 85, Folder 13, Item 3)
  - McCartney, Mary Ellen (Box 89, Folder 45, Item 4)
  - McCrea, Reba M. (Box 94, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - McDiarmid, Dean (Box 88, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - McElroy, Blair (Box 85, Folder 14, Item 3)
  - McGee, Henry (Box 94, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - McGill, William (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - McGrath, Anita (Box 27, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - McGuinness, Brian (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - McKoen, Richard P. (Box 90, Folder 71, Item 15)
  - McKinsey, J. C. C. (Box 89, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - McKinsey, J. C. C. (Box 102, Folder 60, Item 1)
  - McMenamin, Edward B. (Box 90, Folder 72, Item 1)
  - McNaughton, Robert (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - McNaull, Elizabeth M. (Box 85, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Mead, Daniel S. (Box 85, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Meehl, Paul E. (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Meehl, Paul E. (Box 89, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Meehl, Paul E. (Box 90, Folder 63, Item 4)
  - Mehlberg, Henry (Box 80, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Mehlberg, Henry (Box 88, Folder 64, Item 17)
  - Mehlberg, Henry (Box 90, Folder 63, Item 1)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 27, Folder 57, Item 11)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 85, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 85, Folder 16, Item 3)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 85, Folder 17, Item 7)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 89, Folder 30, Item 2)
  - Meiner, Felix (Box 110, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Meiner, Richard (Box 27, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Meiner, Richard (Box 85, Folder 16, Item 15)
  - Melstrads, Ilona (Box 91, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Melstrads, Ilona (Box 91, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Melzer, Yehuda (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 2)
  - Menger, Eva (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Menger, Karl (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Menger, Karl (Box 29, Folder 1, Item 14)
  - Mengershausen, Johannes Von (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Merten, Bernhard (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 4)
  - Meyer, George L. (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - Meyerhoff, Hans (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Meyerhoff, Hans (Box 85, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Meyerhoff, Hans (Box 89, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Meyerhoff, Mary (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 3)
  - Meyerhoff, Mary (Box 80, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Michalos, Alex C. (Box 84, Folder 41, Item 5)
  - Micklesen, Lew R. (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Mikovich, Paul (Box 95, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Miller, David (Box 88, Folder 49, Item 3)
  - Millner, Janice, (1)
  - Millner, M. M. (Box 85, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Mises, Richaard Von (Box 29, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Mises, Richaard Von (Box 90, Folder 81, Item 1)
  - Mitrovich, Paul (Box 95, Folder 21, Item 2)
  - Mitrovich, Paul (Box 95, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Mitrovich, Paul (Box 95, Folder 27, Item 2)
  - Mitrovich, T. (Box 95, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Modick (Box 81, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Modick (Box 81, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 27, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Molina, Cesar Nicholas Flores (Box 88, Folder 51, Item 4)
  - Molina, Cesar Nicholas Flores (Box 88, Folder 66, Item 4)
  - Molina, Cesar Nicholas Flores (Box 88, Folder 67, Item 5)
  - Mondadori, Marco (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Monoson, Charles H. (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Montaque, Richard (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Montaque, Richard (Box 85, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Montaque, Richard (Box 88, Folder 68, Item 4)
  - Montaque, Richard (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 2)
  - Montgomery, Elizabeth (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 4)
  - Moody, Edward F. (Box 27, Folder 60, Item 5)
  - Moody, Ernest A. (Box 80, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Moody, Ernest A. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Moody, Ernest A. (Box 85, Folder 35, Item 1)
  - Moody, Ernest A. (Box 85, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Moody, Ernest A. (Box 102, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Moore, Charles A. (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Moore, Dan Tyler (Box 88, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Moore, R. F. (Box 27, Folder 60, Item 1)
  - Morandini, Michael (Box 88, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Morandino, D. M. (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - Morandino, D. M. (Box 88, Folder 70, Item 11)
  - Morewedge, Prof. Parvis (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Morgenbesser, Sidney (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Morgenbesser, Sidney (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Morgenstern, Oskar (Box 90, Folder 68, Item 2)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 29, Folder 2, Item 22)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 80, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 84, Folder 56, Item 2)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 88, Folder 48, Item 3)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 88, Folder 71, Item 10)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 89, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 89, Folder 41, Item 2)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 89, Folder 66, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 90, Folder 67, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 90, Folder 71, Item 8)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 102, Folder 39, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 102, Folder 47, Item 21)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 102, Folder 48, Item 37)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 102, Folder 51, Item 2)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 102, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 109, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 110, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Morris, Charles W. (Box 110, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Morris, Herbert (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Morris, Herbert (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Morris, Lawrence (Box 95, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Morris, Trude (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 6)
  - Morris, Trude (Box 29, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Morris, Virginia (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Morriset, Lloyd (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Morrison, Paul G. (Box 88, Folder 73, Item 8)
  - Morse, Carl (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Morse, Carl (Box 27, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Mount, George E. (Box 85, Folder 36, Item 1)
  - Muhsam, Henrich (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Mukharji, Shri S. C. (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 2)
  - Mulder, H. L. (Box 88, Folder 73, Item 6)
  - Müller, Johannes (Box 81, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Munzenburg, Joachim (Box 27, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Murphy, Ann (Box 27, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Murphy, Arthur (Box 88, Folder 61)
  - Murphy, Franklin D. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 2)
  - Murphy, Franklin D. (Box 85, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Murphy, Franklin D. (Box 85, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Murphy, Franklin D. (Box 91, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Murphy, Franklin D. (Box 91, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Muschik, Johann (Box 90, Folder 53, Item 2)
  - Muschik, Johann (Box 90, Folder 68, Item 1)
  - Myers, Charles M. (Box 90, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Myers, Francis (Box 85, Folder 39, Item 1)
  - Myers, Francis (Box 88, Folder 64, Item 1)
  - Myhill, John (Box 88, Folder 75, Item 6)
  - Myhill, John (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Myhill, John (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Myhill, John (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Myhill, John (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Myhill, John (Box 109, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Naess, Arne (Box 90, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Naess, Arne (Box 102, Folder 49, Item 21)
  - Naess, Siri (Box 102, Folder 49, Item 11)
  - Nagel, Edith (Box 27, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Nagel, Ernest (Box 27, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Nagel, Ernest (Box 29, Folder 5, Item 21)
  - Nagel, Ernest (Box 88, Folder 75, Item 8)
  - Nagel, Ernest (Box 89, Folder 66, Item 1)
  - Nagel, Ernest (Box 90, Folder 58, Item 1)
  - Nagel, Ernest (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Nagley, Winfield E. (Box 90, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Nagley, Winfield E. (Box 90, Folder 74, Item 13)
  - Nagley, Winfield E. (Box 21, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Nagourney, Herbert (Box 88, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Najder, Zdzislaw (Box 27, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Nakamura, Akaira (Box 27, Folder 34, Item 2)
  - Nakhnikian, Giroge (Box 88, Folder 77, Item 17)
  - Natkin, Marcel (Box 29, Folder 6, Item 4)